(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[28],{444:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t),o.d(t,"FAQs",(function(){return n}));var n=[{id:1,question:"What is ToNote?",answer:"<div>\n      <p>ToNote offers a fully remote way to swear affidavits or get essential documents notarised.</p><br/>\n      <p>Our platform connects you with certified notaries public and allows you  securely sign & notarise important documents, or swear affidavits with  credible notaries as witnesses.</p><br/>\n      <p>Our goal is to create a world where every document shared \n      can be trusted.  We will achieve this by continuously building digital systems of agreement  that are secure, credible and collaborative.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:2,question:"How does ToNote work?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Enjoy a seamless and secure user experience via any internet-enabled desktop, laptop, android or iOS device.</p><br/>\n    <p>On the platform, you can easily share documents, append e-signatures or e-seals, get affidavits and get documents validated virtually by a notary public.</p><br/>\n    <p>To get started, simply register via the website. Start with a free plan or subscribe for a package that best fits your needs.</p><br/>\n    <p>Once you are all signed up, it is advised that you have a fully complete and verified profile. To do this, fill in the required information for verification. Verification on ToNote happens immediately. Once your account has been set up, you can assign team permissions, prepare a document and share with third parties whether they have an account with ToNote or not, swear an affidavit or get any essential document or agreement notarised.</p><br/>\n    <p>On the other hand, as a certified notary public in your country of residence, you can easily create an account on the platform by clicking on “ToNote for Notaries”. We will require a few details to verify that you are certified before ensuring that you are trained and onboarded as a remote online notary public. This may take a day or 2.</p><br/>\n    <p>Once you are trained and have passed the assessments, simply indicate your availability periods for notary sessions and you are open for business.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:3,question:"What are ToNote’s working hours?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Our notaries are available between the hours of 9am and 9pm daily, 7 days a week except public or bank holidays. You can log on to the platform to schedule a notary session at any time. For special requests, send us an email at ask@gettonote.com.</p><br>\n    <i>Note that all sessions are subject to availability of active notaries public. If your request is for an immediate session, you will be placed on a queue and connected with the next available notary on a first come first serve basis.</i></div>"},{id:4,question:"Is e-notarisation by ToNote legal in the country?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>A combination of the Notary Act, Evidence Act and Electronic Evidence Act affirm that ToNote meets all regulatory standards required to operate and enable the remote notarisation of documents. For more regulatory and compliance information, kindly send an email to ask@gettonote.com.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:5,question:"Is notarising on ToNote different from the traditional notarisation?",answer:"\n    <div>\n      <p>ToNote brings convenience and speed to the notarisation process. The traditional approach requires individuals to be in the physical presence of the notary public, and this may involve travelling. The journey to ensure that this happens may be longer</p>\n      <p>and more tedious than necessary.With ToNote, the process and requirements are pretty much the same, with the following benefits:</p><br/>\n    </div>",list:{content:["No physical presence is required to get a document notarised. This can be done at the comfort of your home or office via a video call between you, the notary public and third parties (where necessary).","You and the notary public can now sign, notarise and share documents digitally","As a notary public, you can digitise your physical stamps and seals on the platform.","A digital certificate highlighting all time and personnel related details of each transaction is attached to each notarised document.","Each session is recorded for future audit purposes."],type:"ordered"}},{id:6,question:"Does ToNote use certified notary publics?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Yes. Before you can become a remote online notary on the platform, you must be a commissioned notary public in your country. We screen, train and assess notaries public before certifying them as an online notary public on our platform.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:7,question:"How safe is ToNote with my personal information and contracts? ",answer:'\n    <div>\n      <p>For information on data protection and what we do with personal data please see our <a style="text-decoration:underline;" href="/privacy-policy" target="_blank">Privacy Policy </a>\n      </p>\n    </div>'},{id:8,question:"What are the acceptable forms of ID on ToNote?",answer:"\n    <div>\n      <p>To verify your identity on ToNote you will need any of the following:</p>\n    </div>",list:{type:"unordered",content:["Driver’s license","International passport","National identity card","Voters card"]}},{id:9,question:"How much does it cost to get a document notarised?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Different types of documents may require different notarisation fees. \n    Our pricing is as follows:</p><br/>\n    </div>",footer:"<p>Depending on the outcome of a notary session, additional costs may apply.</p>"},{id:10,question:"What type of document(s) can be signed and notarised on ToNote?",answer:"<div>\n    <p>Any document that requires a signature witness can be prepared, signed and shared on the ToNote platform.</p><br/>\n    <p>Some of the most frequently notarised documents are:</p></div>",list:{type:"unordered",content:["Mortgage closing documents","Loan documents","Financial Statements","Property Deeds","Asset Transfer","Management-Audit Sign off","Wills","Custody and Guardianship Agreements","Power of attorney","Court documents","Promissory note agreement","Affidavits","Articles of Incorporation","Birth Certificates","Wedding Certificates","Examination Certificate/Results","Application forms for Law School Students","Embassy Documents"]}},{id:11,question:"Can I sign, send or notarise documents outside the country?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Absolutely, yes! From wherever you are in the world, you can get your documents notarised without being physically present. You can also sign and share standard agreements with third parties for e-signature.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:12,question:"How secure is ToNote?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Your trust is what we value the most. We have the following security protocols in place to ensure that all your personal information and documents remain safe and secure:</p><br/>\n    </div>",list:{type:"unordered",content:["Identity verification for all platform users","Profile completion monitor and account verification to ensure every user is authenticated and traceable (you will always be informed when a third party user is not verified)","2 factor authentication for access to documentation","Encrypted digital locker for storage of all documents ","Restricted document access based on preset team permissions"]}},{id:13,question:"How can I verify the authenticity of a shared document on ToNote?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>The first step would be to ensure that the document owner is verified on the platform. This means that all information regarding their identity and business has been thoroughly screened by ToNote. Verified users are less likely to share questionable documents as they are easily trackable.</p>\n    <br/>\n    <p>Secondly, always look out for the digital transaction certificate at the end of each document. The digital transaction certificate contains time-stamped details of all actions that took place on a shared document. This means that the document cannot be tampered with.</p>\n    <br/>\n    <p>Thirdly, if you ever suspect that a questionable document has been shared with you, or a document that you shared has been tampered with, simply alert us and we will put a hold on the transaction until further verification has taken place.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:14,question:"What are the various subscription plans?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Please click on the Pricing tab on the homepage of the platform.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:15,question:"How do I migrate from my current plan?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>To migrate from and upgrade your subscription plan, please click on Pricing and Plans on the platform. Review the features, benefits of each plan and select the plan that fits your requirements. For customised solutions and further enquiry, please click on CONTACT SALES to connect with our sales representative who will guide you to a fulfilling subscription plan.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:16,question:"I have a question about the contents of the document or errors in the document, whom do I contact?",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>In most cases, the sender of the document can assist you with these inquiries. We send email notifications on behalf of our users. You can simply click on “reply” via your default email app to contact the sender of the document with questions.</p>\n    </div>"},{id:17,question:"Upload document issues",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>Having issues uploading a document? Please check the following:</p>\n    </div>",list:{type:"unordered",content:["It exceeds 50MB or contains more than 500 pages","It is a .doc, .xls or .ppt. We support .pdf, …..(All document types should be accepted but will automatically convert to PDF."]}},{id:18,question:"Download document issues",answer:"\n    <div>\n    <p>If you are receiving this error when trying to download a document on any browser, please check that the settings for pop-ups and redirects in your browser are set up correctly. You can do this by ensuring that “pop-ups and redirects” are allowed. Under the allow category, please “add gettonote.com and gettonote.ng”</p>\n    </div>"},{id:19,question:"How do I know who sent me a document or note?",answer:"<div><p>The notification email contains the sender name and their email address.</p></div>"},{id:20,question:"How do I download documents or notes from my account?",answer:"\n    <div><p>Here is how to download documents or notes from your account:</p></div>",list:{type:"ordered",content:["Log in to your ToNote account","Search for the document in the search box","You can download a document if it is available in your locker"]}},{id:21,question:"How do I download or print a completed document?",answer:"<div><p>Here is how to download documents or notes from your account:</p></div>",list:{type:"ordered",content:["Log in to your ToNote account","Search for the document in the search box","You can download a document if it is available in your locker","ToNote encourages a greener environment and advises users to share documents electronically to trusted recipients as opposed to printing paper copies."]}},{id:22,question:"As a notary public, how do I get started on ToNote?",answer:"<div><p>Start earning with ToNote by following these steps:</p></div>",list:{type:"ordered",content:["Visit the ‘ToNote for Notaries Public’ tab on our web platform","Sign up and input the required personal information","Upload your ID and Notary certificate or Sworn oath of office documentation","Once your credentials are verified you will be alerted and you can take part in a short Remote Online Notarisation training course and assessment","Digitise your notary stamp, seal and signature automatically","Ensure you have an internet enabled device with audio and video capabilities","Select your preferred schedule for notary sessions","Start earning"]}},{id:23,question:"What is the maximum number of signers ToNote can accommodate?",answer:'\n    <div>\n    <p>ToNote currently accepts up to ten signers per document. Please\n    <a style="text-decoration:underline;" href="/contact-sales" target="_blank">CONTACT SALES</a> for any additional requirement.</p>\n    </div>'},{id:24,question:"Can I get my notarised document physically sent to my address?",answer:"<div><p>No, you cannot get your notarised document sent to you but you can print and download the notarised document.</p></div>"},{id:25,question:"How can a recipient of a notarised document verify a Notarised transaction?",answer:'\n    <div>\n      <p>Always look out for the digital transaction certificate at the end of each document. The digital transaction certificate contains time-stamped details of all actions that took place on a shared document</p><br/>\n      <p>You can <a style="text-decoration:underline;" href="/contact-sales" target="_blank">CONTACT SALES</a> to check and ensure that the document owner is verified on the ToNote platform. This means that all information regarding their identity and business has been thoroughly screened by ToNote. Verified users are less likely to share questionable documents as they are easily trackable.</p>\n    </div>'},{id:26,question:"How do I make my signature electronic? Or how do I upload my electronic signature on ToNote? ",answer:'\n    <div>\n    <p>Do not sign your document before you upload it to ToNote. When you are in session with a notary, you will e-sign by typing your name onto the document. After you Sign Up and complete your profile on ToNote, you will be able to create an electronic signature when working on a document easily. For further enquiry, please \n    <a style="text-decoration:underline;" href="/contact-sales" target="_blank">CONTACT SALES</a>.</p></div>'},{id:27,question:"Do I have to Use Video Conferencing during a Notary session?",answer:"<div><p>Yes! An important requirement for notarisation as stipulated by law is that you must appear or be seen in person. Live video conferencing in real time during your e-notary session makes the process credible.</p></div>"},{id:28,question:"How can I test my webcam?",answer:"<div><p>The easiest way to test your webcam is by clicking on ‘Test My Webcam’ when joining or starting a notary session. This will walk you through to make sure everything is set up correctly.</p></div>"},{id:29,question:"Can you notarise a document that is not written in English?",answer:"<div><p>Not at this time. Please translate your document into English before uploading or simply use available templates on our platform.</p></div>"},{id:30,question:"What type of payments do you accept?",answer:"<div><p>Our system accepts all major credit cards, payment by transfer and USSD.</p></div>"},{id:31,question:"I still have questions",answer:'<div>\n      <p>\n      Send us an email on \n        <a href="mailto:ask@gettonote.com">{ask@gettonote.com}</a> \n      or call us on \n        <a href="tel:+2348146507035">+2348146507035</a>\n      .\n      </p>\n    </div>'}]}}]);